## **CONTACT INFO**

**ADDRESS** 

6538 S. OWENSBORO DR. WEST JORDAN, UT 84604

**PHONE** 

801-350-1688

**EMAIL** 

isaac.ingles@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaac-ingles/

**GITHUB** 

https://github.com/iingles

**PORTFOLIO** 

https://www.isaacingles.com

# Isaac Ingles

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

#### **SUMMARY OF SKILLS**

I'm proficient with HTML5, and CSS3, SASS, LESS, and Javascript. I have experience with Vue, React, and jQuery, as well as the MEVN/MERN stacks. I've built backends with Node and PHP, and I've done some training with Shopify/Liquid. I've learned SQL and GraphQL, and I've used Postgres and MongoDB for various projects. I've also taken courses in C#, C++, and Python. I've learned the basics of Docker and I'm comfortable with a Git workflow.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## **Web Developer**

2012-2013

Axis41

Built and maintained both front-end and back-ends of websites for clients such as Adobe, Best Buy, Sinclair Oil, and OC Tanner.

## **Psychiatric Technician**

2006-2010

**Utah State Hospital** 

Provided direct care to ambulatory psychiatric patients under supervision of a registered nurse. Documented daily patient behavior.

#### **Audiovisual Technician**

2004-2008

2012

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints

Set up, operated, and maintained lighting and sound equipment for Church broadcasts and theatrical productions.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## **Utah Valley University**

Bachelor of Science In Progress - Expected 2021

**Web Design and Development** 

Associate of Applied Science **Digital Communication Technology** 

## **United States Army Reserve**

MOS 12B - Combat Engineer MOS 42A - Personnel Services Specialist